<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools" xmlns:xliff="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2" tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">

  <!-- XTXT: Booster Notification Rule: BNR-DE-0100, STIKO-Empfehlung Booster 12 Jahre; Vorinfo  -->
  <string name="BNR-DE-0100">"The German Standing Committee on Vaccinations (STIKO) recommends a booster vaccination for everyone age 12 and older who has not been diagnosed with a SARS-CoV-2 coronavirus infection and who completed their basic immunization more than three months ago.\n\nThe certificates you have saved indicate that these criteria will soon apply to you and that you have not had a booster vaccination. We therefore wish to point out this recommendation. (Rule DE-BNR-0100)\n\nThis note is based solely on the certificates saved on your smartphone. The data was processed on your smartphone. No information was sent to the RKI or to any third parties in this process."</string>

  <!-- XTXT: Booster Notification Rule: BNR-DE-0110, STIKO-Empfehlung Booster 12 Jahre; Eintritt  -->
  <string name="BNR-DE-0110">"The German Standing Committee on Vaccinations (STIKO) recommends a booster vaccination for everyone age 12 and older who has not been diagnosed with a SARS-CoV-2 coronavirus infection and who completed their basic immunization more than three months ago.\n\nThe certificates you have saved indicate that these criteria apply to you and that you have not had a booster vaccination. We therefore wish to point out this recommendation. (Rule DE-BNR-0110)\n\nThis note is based solely on the certificates saved on your smartphone. The data was processed on your smartphone. No information was sent to the RKI or to any third parties in this process."</string>

  <!-- XTXT: Booster Notification Rule: BNR-DE-0200, STIKO-Empfehlung Optimierung Grundimmunisierung Janssen; Vorinfo  -->
  <string name="BNR-DE-0200">"The German Standing Committee on Vaccinations (STIKO) recommends that anyone who received their basic immunization through a single dose of the Janssen vaccine (Johnson &amp; Johnson) and who has not been diagnosed with a SARS-CoV-2 coronavirus infection get an additional dose of the vaccine to optimize their basic immunization, if their Janssen vaccination took place more than four weeks ago.\n\nThe certificates you have saved indicate that these criteria will soon apply to you and that you have not had any additional vaccinations. We therefore wish to point out this recommendation. (Rule DE-BNR-0200)\n\nThis note is based solely on the certificates saved on your smartphone. The data was processed on your smartphone. No information was sent to the RKI or to any third parties in this process."</string>

  <!-- XTXT: Booster Notification Rule: BNR-DE-0210, STIKO-Empfehlung Optimierung Grundimmunisierung Janssen; Eintritt  -->
  <string name="BNR-DE-0210">"The German Standing Committee on Vaccinations (STIKO) recommends that anyone who received their basic immunization through a single dose of the Janssen vaccine (Johnson &amp; Johnson) and who has not been diagnosed with a SARS-CoV-2 coronavirus infection get an additional dose of the vaccine to optimize their basic immunization, if their Janssen vaccination took place more than four weeks ago.\n\nThe certificates you have saved indicate that these criteria apply to you and that you have not had any additional vaccinations. We therefore wish to point out this recommendation. (Rule DE-BNR-0210)\n\nThis note is based solely on the certificates saved on your smartphone. The data was processed on your smartphone. No information was sent to the RKI or to any third parties in this process."</string>

  <!-- XTXT: Booster Notification Rule: BNR-DE-0400, STIKO-Empfehlung 2. Booster 60 Jahre; Eintritt  -->
  <string name="BNR-DE-0400">"The German Standing Committee on Vaccinations (STIKO) recommends a second booster vaccination for everyone age 60 and older who had their first booster vaccination more than 6 months ago. This recommendation is also valid for persons who were diagnosed with coronavirus after their basic immunization, if the infection occurred more than 6 months ago.\n\nThe certificates you have saved indicate that these criteria apply to you and that you have not had a second booster vaccination. We therefore wish to point out this recommendation. (Rule DE-BNR-0400)\n\nThis note is based solely on the certificates saved on your smartphone. The data was processed on your smartphone. No information was sent to the RKI or to any third parties in this process.\n\nPlease note that for technical reasons, you will also see this note if you have received a booster vaccination that already counts as a second booster vaccination because you have had a previous infection, but have not scanned a certificate of recovery on your smartphone. You can ignore this message in this case. In you are uncertain, please obtain medical advice on how to proceed."</string>

</resources>